<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>~ on chase</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ~ on chase</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo XMin</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>XMin is the first Hugo theme I have designed. The original reason that I wrote it was I needed a minimal example of Hugo themes when I was writing the blogdown book. Basically I wanted a simple theme that supports a navigation menu, a home page, other single pages, lists of pages, blog posts, categories, tags, and RSS. That is all. Nothing fancy. In terms of CSS and JavaScript, I really want to keep them minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo XMin</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>XMin is the first Hugo theme I have designed. The original reason that I wrote it was I needed a minimal example of Hugo themes when I was writing the blogdown book. Basically I wanted a simple theme that supports a navigation menu, a home page, other single pages, lists of pages, blog posts, categories, tags, and RSS. That is all. Nothing fancy. In terms of CSS and JavaScript, I really want to keep them minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Development of Novel Approaches to Anomaly Detection and Surety for Safeguards Data (In Preparation); Natacha Peter-Stein, David Farley, Constantin Brif, Nicholas Pattengale, Chase Zimmerman, Meghan Galiardi, Yifeng Gao, Jessica Lin, Mitchell Negus, Rachel Slaybaugh; Preceedings, 61st Annual Meeting of the Institute of Nuclear Materials Management. Acoustic Signatures in Metal Laser-Powder Bed Fusion (Accepted, delayed until 2021 due to COVID-19); Bradley Jared, David Saiz, Matthew Roach, Scott Jensen, Maher Salloum, Constantin Brif, Chase Zimmerman, Elaine Rhoades; 2021 Annual International Solid Freeform Fabrication Symposium.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>